{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "I wonder my uncle ___ commit such an error.",
      "a": "shall",
      "b": "should",
      "c": "will",
      "d": "must",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Wonder + somebody + should + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I should insist that he ___ accepted as a member, since he is very bad-tempered.",
      "a": "be",
      "b": "will not be",
      "c": "not be",
      "d": "must being",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Insist + that + S + (should) + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It was recommended that the students ___ their reports as soon as they could.",
      "a": "finish writing",
      "b": "finished writing",
      "c": "should finish written",
      "d": "finished the writing",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Finish + V_ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He ignored his doctor's advice that he _________a vacation.",
      "a": "takes",
      "b": "took",
      "c": "would take",
      "d": "take",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- advice that + S + (should) + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "They yielded to her request that they ___ to the result of their experiment.",
      "a": "paid attention",
      "b": "pay attention",
      "c": "paying attention",
      "d": "had paid attention",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- They pay attention to ...(the present simple)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The streets are all wet. It ___ during the night.",
      "a": "must be raining",
      "b": "must have been rain",
      "c": "had to rain",
      "d": "must have rained",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Must + have + past participle: used for saying that you believe something happened in the past",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first thing which a student should bear in mind is that a book ___ for mere amusement.",
      "a": "ought not to be read",
      "b": "ought to not be read",
      "c": "not ought to be read",
      "d": "ought to be not read",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Ought + to + V \n- Ought not + to + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm not used ___ in such a rude way.",
      "a": "being talked to",
      "b": "to being talked to",
      "c": "to be talked to",
      "d": "be talked to",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- to be used to + V-ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want to go to the dentist, but you ___ with me.",
      "a": "need not to go",
      "b": "do not need go",
      "c": "need not go",
      "d": "need go not",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Need not + V = don't need to + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Since Oriental ideas of woman's subordination to man prevailed in those days, she ___ meet with men on an equal basis.",
      "a": "did dare",
      "b": "dare not",
      "c": "dare not to",
      "d": "did dare not to",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Dare not + V = don't dare to + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}